hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft flying
this way that's actually a really big
challenge
flying in third person anyway we are
going to head straight over to sahara oh
actually no i actually need to be in
this room which is interesting i think i
left a box of
no i didn't leave any i need my grass
blocks because at sahara i have prepared
everything that we need for the meeting
room that's right we are now going to
meet up with iska and mumbo
and i need to let you guys in on a
little secret that i've done but i just
need to oh this is
i'm getting actually getting annoyed
that i don't know where all my stuff is
now so
i think at some point i'm going to have
to go through this
over here in sahara i have finished up
the meeting room
and it's even got a little bit of secret
no one's here so they can't do i've also
finished this we'll get we'll get onto
that a bit later but look check this out
i've done redstone some proper redstone
no one helped me with this they don't
know so
as you guys know i kind of explained the
plan before i'm going to during the
meeting pop down this this button
hopefully these guys will sit where oh
that chair's gone i need to put another
chair there but hopefully these guys
will sit in place hit the button and we
all fall through into the infinity room
now here's the second hopefully i'm
going to stand still because i know
what's going to happen
but these guys and i know them they're
going to be walking around and if you
walk around a little bit too much
you're going to fall in the hole but
don't worry it's not a death trap
because there's slime box at the bottom
not a problem at all
so all i've got to do now
is make a second infinity room
here
and they will be so confused
so confused
hopefully both of them fall down here
but even if just one does it i won't
mind and here's the thing when they come
down here and this is all infinity room
even if they do find the way out which
is here
it's gonna say couldn't be bothered to
make a way out although i'm feeling like
i should just close this off
the question i've just realized
the question is everyone
how do i get out
and last one
oh you can fly out all right this now
this is going to be a challenge
perfect i think we're ready
i think we're ready for the meeting all
i've got left to do is add the last two
maps
and walk straight out
the infinity room
is now
complete so now i can as soon as mumbo
and iskall get on can have this meeting
but here's the thing guys i told you i
did some redstone
and i'm going to bet you about 20 green
points
the uh iskawa mumbo
are going to check the redstone that i
did
look at this shoddy shoddy redstone
honestly i'm not sure how it works i
managed to just take each piston at a
time
and it seems to work
although oh this is uh this is an
absolute shambles of redstone there's
holes in it it's not flush it's not
pretty
it's an absolute mess and i'm not really
sure
where
where all the redstone goes
but yes the point is i made this
i i did it by myself i'm proud of myself
and it works but i bet you ten green
points so that they're going to look at
it and laugh at me
which is totally fine because it i know
it's bad but i did my best i did my
absolute best
the last thing to do then is to remove
this button so they don't see it coming
they're not going to just walk in and
press it
and we need to finish off the parrot
party room because this is this is um
this is just a little bit of fun for
when we're having the meetings and i
thought i'd make it look a little bit
nicer in here with some vines going down
we need to add uh some ferns and we've
got to have a pickle in here
you know we just got we got to have some
decorations for the actual birds here
because you know got to have a nice kind
of a nice area
there we go
that looks nice enough and then we just
close it up
why why did you decide sometimes these
parrots forget that they're sitting i
don't know why but they just forget to
sit it's actually really annoying they
just decide to follow you and then we
place the jukebox probably we really
need it close enough so that they
actually do it all right let's let's try
yeah it needs to be closer you see only
these two are dancing in which case the
jukebox almost certainly has to go here
let's see
yeah there we go we've got we got all
five dancing
i guess i just need to leave this bit
open on the side maybe and then i can
walk in put the disc in and then close
up the door no problem but i think we're
probably ready now once i uh move this
into place now here's the thing guys
you can't even warn mumbo and iskall
about what's coming with this infinity
room you can't even let them know
because i'm gonna film it in the same
episode that i set it up so time to go
and wake them up or get them out of bed
or whatever they're doing let's get them
on the server oh and this isn't actually
just a prank by the way we actually do
need to have a meeting we genuinely need
to talk about what's going on with
architects i just thought i'd do this on
the side for a bit of a laugh
welcome to the meeting iscout and mumbo
good to see you back been a while where
have you been where you've been
who are you talking to right now well
both of you really okay okay okay it's
gonna go first where have you been i
yeah i've been around i've been about
i've been doing some bits and bobs here
and there's
mustache man where you been
uh
yeah i haven't been here at all i've
been a really terrible employee for
architect i've actually been i've been
working on my own house
uh as opposed to like the architect
project i i apologize for that so you
haven't seen this room
no i haven't seen any of this stuff i
kind of came by and i i yeah i've i've
been pretty blown away by some of the
things that you guys have been working
on while i've been gone i was actually
pretty blown away as well i've walked
into this room
yeah this is our lead architect that has
built this and he's built it
how how hard is it right to just center
up i'm going to make it
two blocks bigger and then you guys can
shush
let's get this meeting underway hold on
let me put the music on i made this room
specifically for meeting time
there we go
oh cozy background noise
i just realized i don't even get to
enjoy it either
i really appreciate the chair that you
gave me green thank you no problem
i mean that is my chair but i just
didn't say anything
oh course
i
i mean i i love i love the parrots in
the background it's kind of one of those
distractions in the meeting that the
boss will go
all right all right let's not have it
quite that funny today lads let's move
on right and so i'm going to move on
from the beautiful parents i got
something that i want to show you guys
that i've been working on that i've been
dying to show you guys okay go on you
ready for this i worked out
[Music]
sorry sorry sorry okay
what were you talking about iskall you
you've just come back you've done some
business where i have a tool
no
i have done a logo for sahara because
every successful business requires a
logo so check this out i spent absolute
h's on this boom
oh
i've already seen this one
oh yeah sorry that that's actually uh
that's actually a graph of our growth
sorry
here's the logo
oh nice wow that's so i like the cactus
there's so much
tonight
on on hermitcraft
that would make it perfect i i i will
have to play around with those ideas
very nice guys i got to put my suit on
all right i'm going casual this time
there we go okay
wow casual meeting
mambo
so you shouldn't put it you shouldn't
put it in
you can't put it in the meeting room
okay it's as simple as that all right
well we've got more secret matters to
discuss okay so secret that my button
didn't work it's because i'm sitting in
the wrong chair it's gail swapp with me
mumbo go sit in your chair come on okay
okay okay okay
we're working on this i've i've been
tried so hard
there we go oh
good oh goodness
my chair to check what you were doing
there wow okay yeah here we go
welcome to the real news
oh how did i not die
how did i not die how did he know was he
how did he not see that look at my nose
[Laughter]
oh
green what the heck
is this a secondary is that am i in a
sub
infinity room right now did you guys
plan this i did
come here come here come here come here
[Laughter]
oh my goodness this is so creepy welcome
to my world dude yes this is a new one
uh i'm gonna join you i'm going to join
you
so you've made
a new infiniti
you took all ohio armor off you
there's slime blocks underneath
is it
there's sliders
shift
that is the most hilarious thing do you
hold shift yeah
well i feel dumb this was supposed to be
this all went wrong
this was supposed to be my genius plan
to put you guys in in a hole
that was that was the best that was
absolutely hilarious
what's that what the heck take take that
off that's oh wow this is
whoo
yeah i'm close to the person with the
greens now
too much green
[Music]
[Laughter]
but this is what he has done i mean
oh
oh no this is the most difficult thing
in the world
it's hilarious that green is still down
there though i'm the only one you can't
fly out yeah that is ridiculous this is
backfired to the max
i can't even see the difference in the
color either
i can see it but only so slightly
i just want to say oh
goodness
oh
all right maybe we should go back to the
real meeting room no and uh promise me
you won't go and look at the redstone
that i did just just promise me okay
okay i'm totally going to go
i don't think we actually discussed
anything sahara to be honest no i was
too busy trying to get you in the hole
and dying and stuff my bad right yeah
okay
well um i actually did provide a little
like board here
since um most of the building is pretty
much done on my side there's maybe a bit
of interior work to do i thought what i
would focus on is the marketing stuff
but the problem is lads that i can't
really market anything if you can't shop
at sahara the hashtag shop at sahara
doesn't work if you can't shop at sahara
so maybe what we should do is just try
and get like a couple maybe we should
just sell sand just for the start
because i'm sand just just sand
anything just a couple of blocks and
then i can start the marketing you know
getting in there and because then we're
going to grow this business you'd be
happy to hear that there's actually a
functioning ordering system right now we
just need the delivery system because i
installed
decoders so that our shop front is now
speaking with our warehouse i mean
they're not talking english it's more
italian but they are they are now
talking which is great yeah we need we
need the delivery rail though so maybe
in order to progress then we need to
decide where we put this rail down with
the minecart because i personally want
it to be a visible thing straight
through the middle straight through here
big big pipe goes in here
then goes straight in
i'll happily work on that that would be
easy i was expecting you to give me some
technical like just be really delicate
with it have beautiful support
structures and things and you've just
gone straight out the front into the
back
yes big tube big tube so this is the
this is the front thing if i throw in
one cyan terracotta you will see the
first light go on indicating that zahara
has now learned that you've placed an
order and if we wait this is really cool
guys okay i'm proud of this one yep if
we wait
it will light the second light up as
soon as it reaches the warehouse so any
minute now i tried that there we go yeah
oh yes
and now it's picking the
right slot and it picked it boom
and now that's that's it so far okay so
that's that's still impressive but like
how does if i'm a customer how do i know
what it's doing we put signs we'll put
signs yeah 114 is coming out and we can
dye science which would be great for
sahara think about it like dark oak
science with white
text can we put some like little things
here to do if they're waiting for their
order
like mini games
i don't know i like that i like that
idea that's good i was thinking a song
elevated music like
you know
dude
that's quite stressful we can we can we
can do a combination of everything oh
yeah just play the jewels theme
i like that idea oh oh man
can we can we do the zelda thing
[Music]
when your order arrives
but okay we could make we could hum
theme tunes all day long i think it will
both drive the viewers crazy
and also
i mean we've we've finally found a
reason to keep green in sahara once the
building is done yeah greenhouses i'm
just going here yeah let's just let's
just play something
i'm five steps ahead of you dude like
i'll just live in here yeah okay let's
try it i want to try this i'm ordering
now
glass
[Music]
[Laughter]
who needs red stuff when you have
that is totally worth two diamonds
right is there anything left to discuss
or are we just going to keep coming
tunes all day no i think i think that's
pretty like i'm actually surprised at
how close we are to opening actually
yeah yeah so
do we have to stock up on are we going
to sell sand to begin with
yeah i think that's a great idea i'm
gonna get my tube done
i'll get the i'll get the sand
yep
it's gotta do the the redstone stuff
make it work yes
okay
and then all right we've gotta do a
grand opening at some point a really oh
we we have to have an event
red carpet
drinks people come in and we can have
water bottles yeah i like that ariana
grande on the stage
all right sounds like a plan guys it
sounds like we're right on track well
my
meeting did not go to plan i ended up
dying they weren't meant to die
i ended up no one was meant to die there
was meant to be slime blocks but i ended
up i ended up losing my life and all my
levels and stuff and somehow i've now
ended up with ten great korean heads
oh that went all kinds of wrong but i
did make four diamonds
all is not lost so i'm actually feeling
really good now we've got a bit of a
plan
we are a lot
a lot further on than i thought all the
redstone there is done all the redstone
here is done we have no stock yet but if
mumbo makes this big tube that goes over
here iskall links it up we actually have
a functioning shop as long as we stock
it with something and of course the
first thing has to be sand iskall went
ahead and made this which is the
original one and i said
look it is really cool but i said i just
thought that concorps looked cooler and
he was a bit like oh
but then he agreed and then he made this
which is so cool all we got to do
is go and put a mustache on it what
color mustache i i don't know but we
we've definitely got to put a mustache
on this
and that will make it that will make it
so much better in my opinion
in other news looks like someone and i
think i know who good times with scar
has made a train station
i assume it's the train station and this
is part of the hermit rail network which
is insane i think it's a rocket so i
don't know how that is gonna get up
there
that's gonna be quite a quite a
difficult challenge i think so good luck
to scar mumbo's still wearing my face
while we're at sahara i feel like we
should take a good old peek at what our
man poultry man
is up to so let's take a look down the
telescope because this is a magical
telescope you see it's made out of
magical wood and it just shows me
exactly where he is so let's go and have
a look oh he's on the beach doing this
wait he's
what's he
what's he looking at
is he
what what is he gonna look at okay so
he's having a look up in the distance
somewhere
where
ah
someone has called him dearest poultry
man turtleman is in need of eggs chicken
eggs you will be rewarded
what is it
someone's built a giant egg for some
reason well if that isn't some kind of
poultry man signal
i don't know what is the question is
is poultry man going to respond to the
call
well he certainly can no no he's
definitely he's definitely going that
there he goes poultry man
to the red oh he's he's even there
okay so
instead of just giving eggs he's just
he's just spamming chickens
a poultry man that's
you do you poultry man you do you huh
well what do you know poultry man has
saved the day yet again although i'm not
entirely sure
that's what was needed i can't believe
that they were really upset that the
door's not centered and now it's really
upsetting me so i think we're gonna have
to shift this door over just one block
there we go problem solved i probably
should have done that the first time
around but i didn't well i think that's
enough sahara stuff because there's not
a lot for me to do now like i said to
the other guys most of my stuff is done
the building here the building there's
you know bit of interior work still but
for the most part we've got a
functioning building i have actually
started uh completing this up here
because as you know sahara is a green
company and we're going to operate
entirely off of wind power
and uh yeah i've been making this for a
little while now i need to actually
finish this because it's it's actually
more difficult than you would think to
to make a big turbine so yeah i'm going
to finish this off at some point and
have sahara be completely green unlike
those concorp fellas
so i think now we need to continue
working on the elytra course because
this is very exciting and i haven't done
nearly enough on it so the electric
course hasn't changed since the last
episode where you've got to go this way
through here still haven't done that but
i know the course so far and i i think
this is actually quite a nice challenge
because if you do anything like that you
take a bit of damage you get a penalty
point so we're gonna go to the right and
hopefully go through there so what i'm
gonna do is i'm gonna build probably the
next three or four rings that you've got
to go through and then we'll test this
again but the vague idea
is to take this course
kind of around the island of course i
want to take it round the island but i
don't really want to have to put the
rings
somewhere where
it it really kind of ruins the build so
i would love to take it round this area
through the industrial district but i
don't want to put a ring like slap bang
in the middle which could potentially
ruin some of the build so i've got to be
really careful and i've got to think
hard about what i want to do actually
going through this valley would be
awesome i didn't even know this was here
well i'm getting all kinds of ideas here
but i definitely need to take the
electric course
around the island through the most
interesting parts
maybe even through the old wow it feels
like such a long time ago that we had
the hermitcraft civil war
that's crazy well anyway i'm gonna crack
on with the elytra course and i'll be
back with a few more rings to go through
i've added three or four more rings like
i said i would and i've got an idea of
where i want to go next so let's do this
final run through we go straight down
and i'm gonna work out where these
arrows are going to go a bit later on
i've added this ring in and i've made
these a bit tighter spaces to get
through this should be a really fun
course and because it's so long there's
lots of chances to mess up right so you
go through that ring there which i've
linked up between that tree and this
thing that doc made i'm not sure i ever
actually looked at this um nho something
or other well anyway there's a ring here
it then goes through
this direction through this tree which
is also just a ring now this is where it
gets confusing because there's just a
little cave entrance at the moment i
haven't got time in this episode to do
this but basically i'm going to hollow
this whole thing out i'm going to make
this a really decent sized cave decorate
it and everything so you got to pretend
like we're inside right now we're going
through this mountain and it's going to
turn right and come out here so you can
imagine that's quite a lot of excavating
to do and i've started adding the beacon
there but it's going to come out through
there you can see i've got yeah got the
beginnings of a beacon so imagine that
i've done that we're going to exit right
there and then there's a really
difficult part where you've got to go
through this ring here so you can see
that i've added it sort of like had it
go off the side of that and it kind of
just curled round into a ring now that
is an awkward shape to fly through but
that's not the difficult part the
difficult part is you have to pull up
very quickly because there is a mound
there that i'm not getting rid of i
didn't i didn't make that it was
naturally there but you gotta pull up
which
then is up for debate but i know that i
want to head this direction i want to
head over to the industrial district as
i said but i'm thinking what i do maybe
go another cave here but i want to go
through this
as i said earlier and then i will make
my way over to concorp which is just
through here now i'm probably gonna have
to speak to cub and scar no cub mainly
because this is his base i'm gonna have
to ask him
where it's okay to make some circles
because obviously this is a big base but
i'm sure we can make it so that it's
really really cool even maybe even cub
would be up for making this part of the
elytra course i don't know but i'll
speak to him and then find out but i'm
afraid that is all we have time for
today it has been a very busy episode
with that meeting it was a very
important meeting because we now know
where we're at and how close we are to
opening sahara
but anyway thank you very much for
watching everyone and it turns out that
actually saying to everybody that makes
it to the end of the video that if you
do subscribe i would very much
appreciate it it turns out that actually
did work a lot of people subscribed
simply because i said hey i don't do
this very often do you mind subscribing
so if you do feel like subscribing let
me know well no don't let me know just
subscribe see you later bye